<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PMDMAssigment2</string>
    <string name="open_drawer">Open menu</string>
    <string name="close_drawer">Close Menu</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="icon_description">App\'s Logo</string>
    <string name="about_info">App developed by Consuelo López Prieto</string>
    <string name="version">Version 1.0</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome to the Super Mario World</string>
    <string name="character_details">Character details</string>
    <string name="character_list">Character List</string>
    <string name="toast_msg">"You have chosen the character "</string>
    <string name="language">Lenguage</string>
    <string name="spanish">Spanish</string>
    <string name="english">English</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="setting_summary">Enable to English/Disable to Spanish</string>

    <!-- CHARACTERS -->
    <string name="char_description">Character</string>
    <string name="char_abilities">Abilities</string>
    <!-- BOO -->
    <string name="boo_name">Boo</string>
    <string name="boo_description">Mischievous ghosts that tend to roam dark, abandoned places. These ghosts may be creepy, but they are
        also incredibly shy. \n\nThey will freeze in place and cover their eyes if anyone looks directly at them.</string>
    <string name="boo_abilities">Invisibility\n\nWall-through\n\nTeleportation</string>
    <!-- BOWSER -->
    <string name="bowser_name">Bowser</string>
    <string name="bowser_description">The King of the Koopas. Bowser is Mario\'s archrival and is always causing trouble in the Mushroom Kingdom.
        Bowser commands many underlings, including Koopa Troopas, Goombas, Bullet Bills and Shy Guys. \n\nWhenever he sets his sights on the Mushroom Kingdom, his plans are
        often foiled by Mario and friends. Bowser is a mighty foe who possesses incredible strength and can even breathe fire.</string>
    <string name="bowser_abilities">Flamethrower\n\nSuperstrength\n\nShell Atacks</string>
    <!-- BOWSER JR-->
    <string name="bowserjr_name">Bowser Jr</string>
    <string name="bowserjr_description">The only son of Bowser, the King of the Koopas. He is often seen wearing a mask with an intimidating mouth drawn
        on it. Bowser Jr. is small but has inherited great strength from his father. He may throw a tantrum if things don\'t go his way. He is known to cause plenty of trouble
        and can be a bit selfish.</string>
    <string name="bowserjr_abilities">Flamethrower\n\nSuperstrength\n\nAgility</string>
    <!-- DAISY-->
    <string name="daisy_name">Princess Daisy</string>
    <string name="daisy_description">The princess of Sarasaland. Her trademark style includes her yellow dress and flowery accessories. Daisy is cheerful,
        energetic, and enjoys playing a variety of sports with Mario and friends.</string>
    <string name="daisy_abilities">Flowers control\n\nAthletic</string>
    <!-- Goomba-->
    <string name="goomba_name">Goomba</string>
    <string name="goomba_description">Goombas are one of the most iconic enemies in the Super Mario universe. They were originally members of the Mushroom
        Kingdom who turned against the kingdom and joined Bowser\'s forces. \n\nThey are easy to defeat, usually with a simple jump on them.</string>
    <string name="goomba_abilities">Any</string>
    <!-- KOOPA TROOPA-->
    <string name="koopa_name">Koopa Troopa</string>
    <string name="koopa_description">They are one of the oldest and most recognizable enemies. They are anthropomorphic turtles with brightly colored shells,
        usually green or red. They look friendly, but don\'t be fooled: they can be quite challenging in the game.</string>
    <string name="koopa_abilities">Shell Attack</string>
    <!-- LUIGI-->
    <string name="luigi_name">Luigi</string>
    <string name="luigi_description">Mario\'s brother and fellow hero of the Mushroom Kingdom. Luigi is instantly recognisable in his trademark green hat and green shirt.
        Luigi is kind but can be a bit nervous, especially around ghosts. \n\nHowever, his abilities are on par with Mario\'s, so when these brothers team up, there\'s nothing they can\'t achieve.
        Luigi is taller and can jump higher than Mario. If you look closely, you may also notice that the shape of his moustache is a bit different as well.</string>
    <string name="luigi_abilities">High Jumps\n\nGosthbuster</string>
    <!-- MARIO-->
    <string name="mario_name">Mario</string>
    <string name="mario_description">The main hero of the Mushroom Kingdom. Mario is always bright and cheerful and instantly recognisable with his
        blue overalls, red cap and trademark moustache. \n\nHe is a trusted friend of Princess Peach, and he and his brother Luigi are known across the land for their acts of
        bravery. Mario excels at sports including tennis, golf, baseball, football and even kart racing. \n\nHe is good at all of them! He is a plumber by profession but is really
        a jack of all trades.</string>
    <string name="mario_abilities">Superjumps</string>
    <!-- PEACH-->
    <string name="peach_name">Princess Peach</string>
    <string name="peach_description">The beloved princess of the Mushroom Kingdom. She is extremely kind and is always working to create a world where everyone can
        live together happily. Her signature pink dress is quite lovely. \n\nPrincess Peach is always game for a variety of sports, and also enjoys baking and cooking. Princess Peach and Mario
        are good friends and help each other out whenever they can.</string>
    <string name="peach_abilities">Floating</string>
    <!-- ROSALINA -->
    <string name="rosalina_name">Rosalina</string>
    <string name="rosalina_description">A mysterious lady who travels the galaxy accompanied by her family of star-like creatures called Lumas. Rosalina may seem a bit distant,
        but she is actually quite kind-hearted. \n\nShe is the adoptive mother of the Lumas. Though her home is among the stars, she will sometimes join Mario and friends on their adventures.</string>
    <string name="rosalina_abilities">Star Magic\n\nLevitate</string>
    <!-- TOAD -->
    <string name="toad_name">Toad</string>
    <string name="toad_description">A resident of the Mushroom Kingdom who works in service of Princess Peach. Toad has red spots on his head, though others
        of his kind come in a variety of colours. \n\nToad is very cheerful and loyal. He does his best to help Mario and Luigi in their efforts to protect the Mushroom Kingdom from
        Bowser, even if he ends endangering himself in the process.</string>
    <string name="toad_abilities">Velocity</string>
    <!-- WALUIGI -->
    <string name="waluigi_name">Waluigi</string>
    <string name="waluigi_description">Wario\'s pal and accomplice. Waluigi is the self-proclaimed rival of Luigi. Waluigi is willing to put in a lot of effort
        to best Mario and Luigi, if only to annoy them. His long arms and long legs help keep him competitive at sports.</string>
    <string name="waluigi_abilities">Trickery\n\nCheater</string>
    <!-- WARIO -->
    <string name="wario_name">Wario</string>
    <string name="wario_description">The self-professed archrival of Mario. Wario wears purple overalls, a yellow hat, and has an instantly recognisable zigzag moustache.
        \n\nWario and Mario have known each other since they were babies. He\'s got a boisterous personality and doesn\'t sweat the small things. He loves garlic and making money.</string>
    <string name="wario_abilities">Superstrength</string>
    <!-- YOSHI -->
    <string name="yoshi_name">Yoshi</string>
    <string name="yoshi_description">Mario\'s dependable companion who hails from Yoshi\'s Island. He is green, but others of his kind may be other colours such as red,
        blue, pink and yellow. \n\nYoshi is kind and carefree. He uses his long tongue to gobble up fruit and enemies, which he can turn into eggs for throwing.</string>
    <string name="yoshi_abilities">Lick\n\nEggthrower\n\nLong Jumps</string>
</resources>